

Ruslan Mirasov

Frontend Developer

SUMMARY

I am an experienced frontend developer with a commercial background spanning since 2015, having worked both in web studios and as a freelancer. My technology stack includes proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. I excel in collaborative team environments and have a quick-learning mindset. Currently seeking a company for long-term collaboration.

CONTACT INFORMATION

- . +49 (177) 839-11-02
- info@mirasov.dev
- Germany, Berlin
- Telegram
- (G) GitHub
- www.mirasov.dev

HARD SKILLS

- HTML GIT
- CSS3 / SCSS REST API
- JavaScript
 Webpack / Parcel
- TypeScriptNode.js
- React / Redux MongoDB

SOFT SKILLS

- Team work
- Eager to learn
- Attentive
- Committed
- Punctual

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian native
- Russian native
- English upper-Intermediate
- German intermediate

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Nectar Beauty (HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP)

Development of adaptive, multi-page, multi-lingual website for Beauty salon "Nectar". **Role:** Full-stack developer (individual commercial project)

Tasty treats (HTML / CSS / JavaScript / REST API)

A website of Teasty treats company. Responsible for the development of: Header, Hero Section, the functionality of adding a recipe to favourites and Local Storage.

Role: Front-end developer (team non-commercial project)

The Watch Spot (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)

Landing Page for "The Watch Spot" company, producing premium watch collections. **Role:** Team lead (team non-commercial project)

Oreo (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)

Development of an interactive game for the company "Mondelez".

Role: front-end developer (individual commercial project)

Rabstvo (HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / Wordpress / WooCommerce / ACF)

Development of a website with blog and online shop functionality for Rabstvo, a company promoting music labels. Landing the site on CMS Wordpress.

Role: Full-stack developer (individual commercial project)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing agency "Beauty Alliance"

2017 - 2022 | Frontend developer (remotely)

Marketing agency "Mokselle"

2015 - 2017 | Frontend developer (remotely)

EDUCATION

Fullstack Developer

2023 - 2024 | <u>IT School GoIT</u>

Web Developer "Basic"

2014 - 2015 | <u>IT School Skillbox</u>

Mechanical engineering technology specialist

2005 - 2011 | Pryazovskyi State Technical University.